[{
    "theme": "20 verbos más comunes en español",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "to be (essential/permanent)",
            "answers": ["ser"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to be (states/locations)",
            "answers": ["estar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to have",
            "answers": ["tener"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to do, to make",
            "answers": ["hacer"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to go",
            "answers": ["ir"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to say, to tell",
            "answers": ["decir"]
        },
        {
            "question": "can, to be able to",
            "answers": ["poder"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to see",
            "answers": ["ver"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to give",
            "answers": ["dar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to know (facts/information)",
            "answers": ["saber"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to want, to love",
            "answers": ["querer"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to arrive",
            "answers": ["llegar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to pass, to happen",
            "answers": ["pasar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "should, to owe",
            "answers": ["deber"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to put, to place",
            "answers": ["poner"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to seem, to appear",
            "answers": ["parecer"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to stay, to remain",
            "answers": ["quedarse"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to believe",
            "answers": ["creer"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to speak, to talk",
            "answers": ["hablar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to carry, to wear",
            "answers": ["llevar"]
        }
    ]
}]
